I took one look... and I couldn't speak.
Polished, she was so beautiful
it was as if she'd been reborn.
Her melancholy eyes sparkled like stars.
So beautiful.
Stop running from reality.
Lady Marie refused your proposal, Master.
I... I can't do this!
Don't thrust reality at me, Mio.
You're always, always so cruel!
This is my duty.
Still, who would have imagined that you'd mistakenly propose to the wrong sister.
Well, how could I have known?
That night, it was Marie's birthday.
The girl sitting alone in the darkness...
Who would think that she
was the star of the party?
My father, Duke Alfred
Granado, had two wives.
Episode 2 "Marie, I Want to Marry You"
If the cat lay around like
trash, it became trash.
If the trash cried, "meow,"
then it became a cat.
And then, with me, it—
Stop playing games!
Don't you understand your position here?
Know your place!
The daughter of a noble family equal to the
duke's, my father Alfred's official wife,
Lady Laura.
And an Ipsandrian traveling performer
he took as his concubine,
my mother, Liu Liu.
I thought I heard a commotion.
Here. Eat this and be quiet.
That's something I baked.
You're quite trusting to eat it, aren't you?
That's because it's really yummy!
I love it!
Do you? And what else do you like?
Let's see. Cake and cream
puffs and chocolate cookies!
I love sweets!
I like sweets, too.
When I make sweets, I don't have
to think about unpleasant things.
Next time, I'll make some
chocolate cookies for you.
All right!
It is true that Laura is my official wife,
but all the children she has
borne me have been girls.
Which is why the one to
inherit my dukedom...
will be Kyros.
No!
Open your eyes! Mother!
Why? Why would you take poison?
Why had the woman who had
been so kind to me...
chosen death of her own free will?
After Liu Liu was elevated to
the position of official wife,
she said that she was no more than a
concubine and left the duke, taking me with her.
And I, in order to survive in this land,
attained the status of count
through my own efforts.
But I hate gatherings of high society,
and I evaded any talk of
marriage to noble daughters.
Hey there, my friend!
So you've finally shown your face.
If you invite me, then I have no choice.
Did you receive one as well?
An invitation from a rural baron.
Luiphon, you got one, too?
It seems that they must have sent one to every
bachelor who is wealthy or from the great houses.
Baron Shaderan's family's troubles with
money are well-known among the aristocracy.
It's blatantly clear that this birthday
party is a pretext for marketing his daughter.
Honestly. It's despicable.
But according to rumors,
she is quite the beauty.
I have a fiancée, so I
couldn't possibly go,
but Kyros, why don't you attend?
Not interested.
Count Granado?
You're welcome to these if you'd like.
Yes, thank you.
The ladies do like you, don't they?
They like me? All they see
is my title and my money.
Deep down, those women
all despise my heritage.
Well, the average noble daughter detests
Ipsandros as a land of barbarians, you know?
He's so wonderful.
But the color of his skin...
You know about his mother.
I understand how you feel,
but you can't remain a bachelor forever, can you?
You are a count and the
only son of a ducal house.
If you stay single, there won't be
anyone to carry on the duke's line.
I know.
What sort of lady will be
able to win your heart?
I greatly look forward to finding out.
As if such a day would ever come.
No, he's right.
The daughter of an impoverished
baron might be just right.
And if it's only to be a
marriage of convenience,
then someone easy to manage would be best.
Love...
That's something I never need to feel.
At least, that's what I thought.
Personally, I love stories from Ipsandros.
And yet, I've fallen in love with her.
I wanted to speak with her more,
but she slipped through my fingers.
By the way, I was wondering if this year—
Apologies. Are you Baron Shaderan?
Where is your daughter?
The star of the night is right over there!
Please! Take our daughter as your bride!
Oh, my dear! You've had too much to drink!
No, I haven't!
I was told that the House of Shaderan
has the elder daughter Anastasia
and the younger Marie.
"The star of the night"?
If she's Marie, the younger
sister whose birthday it is,
then the one I met was the
older sister, Anastasia!
I searched for her everywhere.
But no matter how hard I looked...
I couldn't find her.
I decided to send a letter.
I wanted not the younger sister Marie,
but the older sister Anastasia as my wife.
Excellent! A reply has arrived!
After that, I became incredibly busy.
To offer my fiancée the finest hospitality,
I arranged for dresses,
jewels, and new servants.
Anastasia
Is
Life
I even acquired a body pillow to
hold through my sleepless nights.
But...
The carriage... fell?
And then, amid my heartbreak and despair...
the woman I'd thought bore
the name Anastasia arrived.
Marie Shaderan.
Honestly, Master, you are such a fool.
Though, my own knowledge
was lacking as well.
And now... I've been rejected?
Accepting the truth as truth
is a wonderful thing, indeed.
Mio, couldn't you be a little
less... direct about this?
Well then, Master, can you explain this?
You turned away and silently
shunned Lady Marie's new look.
Also, saying, "Send Marie
Shaderan away" wasn't optimal.
Master, I am certain that Lady
Marie believes that you hate her.
If I clear up that misunderstanding, do you
think she will happily become my wife?
I do not know.
But for now, just give it your best.
After all, Master, you are the one
who feels a one-sided love here.
Yes, you're right.
Let's go and see Marie.
What I want to see...
is her smile!
Worn out, tattered clothing.
My well-thumbed, beloved book.
That is all that this world has
bestowed upon me, and yet...
Who is this?
Yes? Come in.
Mio... and Lord Kyros?
I-I am so sorry for the
rudeness I displayed earlier!
Rudeness? What are you talking about?
It was all so sudden that I lost
my composure. I am truly sorry.
No, I'm the one who should apologize.
Please lift your head.
I-It seems that a huge
misunderstanding lies between us.
First of all, I don't hate you, Marie.
Second, I had thought that you'd come
to this palace of your own free will.
I'm sorry for making such an assumption.
I truly do want to welcome you as my wife.
Of course. Thank you for having me.
What?
Wh-When I said that I couldn't be betrothed to
you, it was only because I was so shocked.
R-Really?
Yes. I have no intention of refusing you.
I have a general understanding of
your situation, your lordship.
To inherit the title of duke, you
must marry a woman of noble birth.
However, finding a bride has been difficult.
What you're saying is true, but...
If it weren't, then someone of your standing,
sir, would never attend a poor baron's party.
There, as your potential partner in a
marriage of convenience, you fell for my sister,
the beautiful Anastasia.
I-I shouldn't have said all that!
I'm so terribly sorry.
Due to the accident, I, the useless
younger sister, have come to you,
but I assure you, I know my place.
Your Lordship, please treat me in
whatever manner serves you best.
Wait! Please, just wait!
It's true that I had a political marriage
in mind when I went to that party.
But that night, my feelings changed!
That letter was no facade.
I meant every word!
Yes, I know. Your feelings for Anastasia
were conveyed quite clearly.
No! That's where you have it wrong!
This doesn't make any sense.
Both of you, it is time for dinner.
I believe it would be best if you
continued your discussion as you eat.
GROWWWWL
Yes, you're right. I'm so hungry
I feel like I'm about to die.
Everything is delicious!
This is incomparably better than our meals!
Marie.
This will be no marriage of convenience.
The proposal letter that
I sent to Anastasia...
I simply got her name confused with yours,
the lady I met in the garden that night.
The one I want to marry is you, Marie.
I'm honored.
You don't believe me, do you?
Lord Kyros, you are a kind person.
There's no need to be so
careful of my feelings.
I knew you didn't believe me.
For anyone born into
nobility, marriage is a duty.
It's the same for Lord Kyros.
No, his responsibilities and
mine can't be compared.
I'm certain that he'll take a concubine.
I may end up wearing tattered
clothes and working again.
But I don't mind.
Life will be much the same
as it always has been.
Um, is there anything else?
I love you, Marie.
Love?!
Who is in love? With whom?
This makes the least sense of all!
Whatever the case,
we agree on our betrothal.
The engagement ceremony
will be in three months.
I'll arrange for everything.
You don't have to worry about a thing.
Of course. I understand.
I hope you will enjoy your
life here in the meantime.
P-Pardon me!
Just once, I would like to go back home.
To the Shaderan house? Why?
My father didn't think that the
betrothal would come to pass.
I was to serve as your
comfort for one night.
After forming a bond with you,
he was insistent that
I be kicked out and return to him.
What?!
I-I never imagined this turn of events either,
so I must return home to receive instructions.
Mio.
Of course.
Lady Marie, if you would wait just a moment.
H-Have I done something
disrespectful toward them?
No, all I've been is disrespectful.
I am afraid to say, Lady Marie,
that you are forbidden to return
to your parents' house.
Wh-Why?
The master's orders.
Should Lord or Lady Shaderan come to visit,
we ask that you receive the master's
permission before meeting them.
Lady Marie, may I ask you something?
Why are you under the impression
that you are ugly?
B-Because my mother and father...
My hair is covered in balls
of lint. I have freckles.
They always showed me my tattered,
raggedy self in the mirror.
If you'll permit me to say, Lady Marie,
of those things you just mentioned,
the only thing here is the mirror.
Please, look into it as much as you like.
Look into the mirror?
And what will happen if I do?
After all, the real me isn't this
person I've never seen before.
It doesn't feel real at all.
Wh-What is this?!
It's so fluffy and warm!
It's like the world in a fairytale.
A magnificent, white-walled palace.
Beautiful, glittering clothes.
Wonderful lady attendants.
And... a count with beautiful green eyes.
It really is...
like a dream.
That's right.
I'm certain that when I wake,
the spell will be broken,
and all that will be left
is me in my tatters.
I love you, Marie.
I'm so embarrassed! Having a
dream like this is just...
But if it is a dream,
I don't want to wake up yet.
After all...
If this is a dream, then it's
all right for me to feel happy.
I had such a strange dream last night.
Now, I have to light the fire in the stove,
wake everyone in the family, and...
Wait.
Oh. I'm still dreaming, aren't I?
Then it wouldn't hurt
to enjoy this a little more.
Lady Marie?
Are you awake?
Y-Yes, I'm awake!
Please pardon the intrusion.
Good morning, Lady Marie.
G-G...
Good morning!
What are you doing, Lady Marie?
Y-You were kind enough to bow so politely
to me that I had to bow even lower.
Why? Please, be at your ease here.
Um, who are these ladies?
Lady Marie, you have officially
become the master's fiancée.
From now on, we three will
look after your daily needs.
Allow me to introduce you.
They are Hannah and Ilza.
My name is Ilza.
My name is Hannah.
Oh, Marie.
Why won't you believe my feelings for you?
True, it's my fault for getting you and
your sister's names mixed up, but...
If there's anything you
lack, I'll give it to you!
So, please... open your heart
to me, just a little.
Next time, "A Life I Saw in a
Dream, and a Dream-like Life."
Episode 3 "A Life I Saw in a Dream, and a Dream-like Life"
Please, you must come and watch!